Guide to the Inge Morath Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1896-2001; Series I; 136.99; (550 boxes)
  - Contact Sheets
    - Personal Set
      - 1969-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-44) (Box 71)
        Includes Jay Presson Allen, screenwriter, playwright, director, producer and novelist; Lauren Bacall, actress; James Blake, author; Joseph Duffey, educator; Cleve Gray, painter, and his wife, Francine du Plessix Gray, author and critic; Prince Sadruddin Aga Khan, United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees; Arthur Miller; Jerzy Kosiński, novelist; Inge Morath; Robert C. Osborn, artist and author; Harrison E. Salisbury, author and journalist, and his wife, author Charlotte Young Salisbury; Benjamin Spock, pediatrician; Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator; William Styron, author; William H. M. Talbot, sculptor; and Teresa Wright, actress
      - 1969-02. Olga Andreyeva Carlisle, writer, and Henry Coffin Carlisle, translator, novelist, and activist (Rolls 1-2) (Box 71)
        Includes Jerzy Kosiński, novelist
      - 1969-03. Prague, Czechoslovakia; Vienna and Graz, Austria; and Sperlonga, Rome, Pompeii, and Gaeta, Italy (Rolls 1-9) (Box 71)
        Includes Libor Fára, sculptor and painter; Anna Fárová, art historian; Václav Havel, author and philosopher; Arnold Keyserling, philosopher and theologian; Arthur Miller; and Jiří Mucha, journalist and author
        Also includes images from the funeral of Morath's father, Edgar Morath
      - 1969-04. Rose Burgunder Styron, poet and wife of William Styron (Rolls 1-2) (Box 71)
      - 1969-05. Peter Blume, painter and sculptor (Roll 1) (Box 71)
      - 1969-06. Hans Richter, painter, graphic artist, and producer, in Kettletown State Park, Connecticut (Rolls 1-3) (Box 71)
      - 1969-07. Gladys Brooks Thayer, philanthropist (Roll 1) (Box 71)
      - 1969-08. The Reason Why, film written by Arthur Miller, and directed by Paul Leaf (Rolls 1-5) (Box 71)
      - 1970-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-58) (Box 72)
        Includes Alexander Calder, sculptor, and his wife Louisa James Calder; Corinne Alsop Cole, politician; Malcolm Cowley, author, and his wife, Muriel Maurer Cowley; Joseph Duffey, educator; Naum Gabo, sculptor; Francine du Plessix Gray, author and critic; Vladimir Horowitz, pianist and composer; Jerzy Kosiński, novelist; Fredric March, actor, and his wife, actress Florence Eldridge March; George McGovern, United States Senator from South Dakota; Arthur Miller; Nicolas Nabokov, composer and author; Robert C. Osborn, artist and author; Hans Richter, artist; Harrison E. Salisbury, author and journalist, Stephen Spender, poet and author; Olga Spessivtseva, dancer; William Styron, author; William H. M. Talbot, sculptor; and Louis Untermeyer, poet
        Also includes images of studio of Saul Steinburg, cartoonist and illustrator, as well as of the Shelton Historical Society
      - 1970-02. Francine du Plessix Gray, author (Roll 1) (Box 72)
      - 1970-03. Japan (Rolls 1-9) (Box 72)
        Includes Kōbō Abe, author, photographer, and inventor; Aleksei N. Leontiev, psychologist; Arthur Miller; John Nathan, translator; Kenzaburō Ōe, author; and Tsuji Seimei, ceramicist
      - 1970-04. Cambodia (Rolls 1-3) (Box 72)
      - 1970-04. Harrison E. Salisbury, author and journalist, and his wife, author Charlotte Young Salisbury (Rolls 1-2a) (Box 73)
        Includes images of the studio of Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator
      - 1970-05. Bangkok, Thailand, and Hong Kong (Rolls 1-5) (Box 72)
      - 1970-06. Hong Kong (Roll 1) (Box 72)
      - 1970-07. Earth Day in New York (Rolls 1-3) (Box 72)
      - 1970-08. Alexander Tolstoy Foundation, Valley Cottage, New York (Rolls 1-3) (Box 72)
        Includes Arthur Miller and Alexandra Tolstaya, daughter and secretary of Leo Tolstoy, as well as Robert Whitehead, theatre producer, and his wife, actress Zoe Caldwell
      - 1970-09. Jean Stein, author and editor, and her children, Katrina vanden Heuvel and Wendy vanden Heuvel (Rolls 1-2) (Box 72)
      - 1970-10. Wedding of Jane Ellen Miller, daughter of Arthur Miller and Mary Grace Slattery, and Tom Doyle (Rolls 1-3) (Box 72)
      - 1970-11. Vadim Andreyev, Washington, Connecticut (Roll 1) (Box 72)
      - 1970-12. Naum Gabo, sculptor in Middlebury, Connecticut (Roll 1) (Box 72)
      - 1970-13. A Memory of Two Mondays, by Arthur Miller, and produced by NET Playhouse (Rolls 1-17) (Box 72)
        Includes actors George Grizzard, Bernard Hughes, Kristoffer Tabori, and Jack Warden, as well as actresses Estelle Parsons and Catherine Burns
      - 1971-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-58) (Box 73)
        Includes Peter Blume, painter and sculptor, and his wife, Grace Douglas "Ebie" Blume; Philip Grausman, sculptor, and his wife, and Martha Grausman; Arthur Miller; and Robert Whitehead, theatre producer, and his wife, actress Zoe Caldwell
      - 1971-02. Ruth Simon, yoga instructor (Rolls 1-4) (Box 73)
      - 1971-03. William Styron, novelist and essayist, and Arthur Miller (Rolls 1-2) (Box 73)
      - 1971-05. Creation of the World and Other Business, by Arthur Miller, production meeting (No rolls recorded) (Box 73)
        Includes Boris Aronson, scene designer; Harold Clurman, theater director and critic; Arthur Miller; and Robert Whitehead, theatre producer
      - 1972-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-41) (Box 74)
        Includes Leonard Bernstein, composer, author, and pianist, and his wife, actress Felicia Montealegre; Katharine "Kay" Brown Barrett, agent for Arthur Miller; Olga Andreyev Carlisle, author; Phyllis Jackson, literary agent; Frederic March, actor; Julien Levy, art dealer; Jerzy Kosiński, novelist; Gjon Mili, photographer; Rebecca Miller; Andrea Morath; Sigrid "Gigi" Spaeth, graphic designer; Saul Steinberg, cartoonist and illustrator; Augusta Talbot, painter; and Yevgeny Yevtushenko, poet
        Also includes Philip Grausman, sculptor, and his wife, and Martha Grausman, with the former sculpting a bust of Arthur Miller; as well as the home of William Styron, novelist and essayist, and his wife, poet Rose Burgunder Styron
        Additionally, includes Boris Aronson, scene designer; Arthur Miller; and Robert Whitehead, theatre producer; with a model for "Creation of the World and Other Business"
        The set also includes images of an assembly of the New Haven Women's Liberation
      - 1972-02. Israel (Rolls 1-9) (Box 74)
        Includes locations in Hulda, Jaffa, Jericho, Jerusalem, Galilee, Sea of Galilee, and Masada
        Includes professors at the Weizmann Institute of Science in Rehovot, including David Nachmansohn, biochemist; Michael Sela, immunologist; and Igal Talmi, nuclear physicist
        Also includes Moshe Dayan, Minister of Defense; Amos Elon, journalist and author; Amos Oz, author; and Jeshajahu "Shaike" Weinberg, director of Cameri Theater in Tel Aviv; as well as sculptors Siona Shimshi and Dani Karavan
      - 1972-03. Alexander Calder, sculptor, and his wife Louisa James Calder (Rolls 1-2) (Box 74)
        Includes locations in Saché and Chinon in Indre-et-Loire, France, as well as images of Arthur Miller, Rebecca Miller, and Werner Morath
      - 1972-04. Heinrich Böll, writer, in Cologne, Germany (Rolls 1-2) (Box 74)
        Includes Arthur Miller and Werner Morath
      - 1972-05. Matthew Josephson, journalist and author, in Sherman, Connecticut (Rolls 1-2) (Box 74)
      - 1972-06. Creation of the World and Other Business, by Arthur Miller, directed by Gerald Freedman, at the Shubert Theatre, New York City (Rolls 1-34) (Box 74)
        Includes Harold Clurman, theater director and critic; Arthur Miller; and Robert Whitehead, theatre producer
      - 1972-07. Photographs for Ruth Bluestone Simon, Relax & Stretch: The East-West Approach to Health & Beauty (New York: Walker, 1973) (Rolls 1-50) (Box 74)
      - 1973-01. Studies of nudes by Philip Grausman, sculptor, as well as images of Rebecca Miller (Rolls 1-35) (Box 75)
      - 1973-02. Connecticut (Rolls 1-30) (Box 75)
        Includes Alexander Calder, sculptor, and his wife Louisa James Calder; Olga Andreyev Carlisle, author, and her niece; William Sloane Coffin, clergyman and activist, and his wife, Harriet Gibney Coffin; Francine du Plessix Gray, author and critic; Allan Kern, dairy farmer in Woodbury, and his son; Arnold Keyserling, philosopher and theologian; Arthur Miller; Rebecca Miller; Hans Richter, painter; and Robert Whitehead, theatre producer, and his wife, actress Zoe Caldwell
        Also includes views of a peace march in Danbury; Miss Porter's School in Farmington; a farm auction, Rumsey Hall School in Washington, and a camel on Weekeepeemee Road in Woodbury
      - 1973-03. Saint Thomas, United States Virgin Islands (Rolls 1-2) (Box 75)
        Includes Everett B. Birch, attorney, and Pomeranian dogs
      - 1973-04. Rose Burgunder Styron, poet and wife of William Styron, in Roxbury, Connecticut, for her book, Thieves' Afternoon (New York: Viking Press, 1973) (Rolls 1-4) (Box 75)
      - 1973-05. Oregon (Rolls 1-2) (Box 75)
        Includes Robert A. Miller, son of Arthur Miller and Mary Grace Slattery, and Erica, baby, as well as landscapes near Madras (Chennai), India
      - 1973-06. Nightwalk, by Megan Terry, Sam Shepard, and Jean-Claude van Itallie, produced by The Open Theater, and directed by Joseph Chaikin (Rolls 1-10) (Box 75)
      - 1973-07. Joseph Brodsky, poet and essayist (No rolls recorded) (Box 76)
        Includes Alexander Liberman, magazine editor, publisher, painter, photographer, and sculptor, in Warren, Connecticut, as well as the home of Jerzy Kosiński in New York.
        Also includes Joseph Chaikin, director and playwright, and Heinrich Böll, author
      - 1973-08. Janet Flanner, writer and journalist (Rolls 1-2) (Box 76)
        Includes images of Roxbury, Connecticut, as well as Arthur Miller and Natalia Danesi Murray, writer, editor, and radio commentator
        Also includes Inge Morath's dresses by designer Cristobal Balenciaga
      - 1973-09. Joan Maxine Miller Copeland, actress and the younger sister of Arthur Miller (Rolls 1-2) (Box 76)
      - 1973-10. Pilobolus dance company rehearsing in Roxbury, Connecticut (Rolls 1-2) (Box 76)
        Includes William Sloane Coffin, clergyman and activist, with Rebecca Miller, and Rebecca and Laurie Yelding at the Lake Quassapaug Park in Middlebury, Connecticut
      - 1973-11. Olga Andreyev Carlisle, writer (Roll 1) (Box 76)
        Includes close-up photographs for a book jacket, probably Olga Andreyev Carlisle, Grosse Photographen unserer Zeit: Inge Morath (Luzern: C. J. Bucher, 1975)
        Also includes images of Rebecca Miller
      - 1973-12. Flight of Flying Colors of South America, a Douglas DC-8-62 airplane for Braniff International Airways designed by Alexander Calder, to Dallas, Los Angeles, and Chicago on Calder's 75th birthday (Rolls 1-14) (Box 76)
        Includes members of the Calder family; Robert C. Osborn, artist and author, and his wife, museum director Elodie Courter Osborn; Dorothy Canning Miller, curator; and Klaus Perls, art dealer
      - 1973-13. Vadim Andreyev, poet, and Alyusha Andreyev (Roll 1) (Box 76)
        Includes their daughter Olga Andreyev Carlisle, author, in Washington, Connecticut
      - 1973-14. Torin Corporation, portraits of directors for an annual report (Rolls 1-7) (Box 76)
      - 1974-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-26A) (Box 76)
        Includes images in Connecticut include the home of William Styron, novelist and essayist, and his wife, poet Rose Burgunder Styron, in Roxbury; commencements at Rumsey Hall School and Wykeham Rise School in Washington; Ruth Stout, gardener and author, probably in Redding; parade during the Blessing of the Fleet Day in Stonington; Philip Johnson Glass House in New Canaan; Yale University campus in New Haven; Apple Blossom Festival in Bethel; Goshen Fair in Goshen; Howard Rower, reverend of Church of Scientology, officiating a wedding; and a party held by or for Francine du Plessix Gray, author and critic
        Also includes Arthur Miller in Dearborn, Michigan, and in Venice, Italy, as well as portraits of Stanley Silverman, composer, as an illustrations for poems by Boris Pasternak
      - 1974-02. Prague, Czechoslovakia (Rolls 1-3) (Box 77)
        Includes Anna Fárová, art historian; Marta Kadlečíková, novelist; Ivan Klíma, novelist and playwright; Pavel Kohout, novelist; Jiří Mucha, journalist, author, screenwriter; and Ludvík Vaculík, journalist and author
      - 1974-03. Budapest, Hungary (Roll 1) (Box 77)
        Includes views of Halászbástya (Fisherman's Bastion), a terrace in Budapest, and Maria Enzersdorf, Austria, as well as portraits of Gyula Illyés, poet and novelist
      - 1974-04. Vienna, Austria (Rolls 1-2) (Box 77)
        Includes Karlskirche, Schönbrunn Palace, and Upper Belvedere
      - 1974-05. John F. Wharton, lawyer in entertainment law (Rolls 1-3) (Box 77)
      - 1974-06. Party of Charlotte Young Salisbury, New York (Roll 1) (Box 77)
      - 1974-07. After the Fall, by Arthur Miller, and produced by Gilbert Cates Productions and distributed by the National Broadcasting Company (Rolls 1-4) (Box 77)
        Includes actress Faye Dunway and actor Christopher Plummer
      - 1974-08. Up from Paradise, musical with a book and lyrics by Arthur Miller and music by Stanley Silverman, directed by Arthur Miller, at the Power Center for the Performing Arts, Ann Arbor, Michigan (Rolls 1-14) (Box 77)
      - 1974-09. No story at this number (No rolls recorded) (Box 77)
      - 1974-10. Works by Augusta Talbot at the Gallery in West Cornwall, Connecticut (Roll 1) (Box 77)
      - 1974-11. No story at this number (No rolls recorded) (Box 77)
      - 1974-12. No story at this number (No rolls recorded) (Box 77)
      - 1974-13. William Sloane Coffin, clergyman and activist, and Harriet Gibney Coffin at Marsh Island, Maine (Rolls 1-4, includes color photographs) (Box 77)
      - 1974-14. Carlisle House Inn, Nantucket, Massachusetts (Rolls 1-4) (Box 77)
      - 1974-15. Alan Schwartz in Nantucket, Massachusetts (Roll 1) (Box 77)
      - 1974-16. Studio of Philip Grausman, sculptor, and his wife, and Martha Clarke, choreographer and director (Rolls 1-3) (Box 77)
      - 1974-17. Nell Dorr, photographer, in Washington, Connecticut (Roll 1, includes color photographs) (Box 77)
      - 1974-18. Abe Ajay, sculptor, in Bethel, Connecticut (No rolls recorded) (Box 77)
      - 1974-19. Arthur Miller and Inge Morath in Europe (Rolls 1-5) (Box 77)
        Includes Brussels, Belgium; Cologne, Germany; Lucerne, Switzerland; and Venice, Italy
      - 1974-20. Copy photographs (No rolls recorded) (Box 77)
        Includes Arthur Miller when he wrote Death of a Salesman, as well as portraits of his mother, Augusta Barnett Miller, and sister, Joan Maxine Miller Copeland
        Also includes a portrait of Inge Morath by photographer by Henri Cartier-Bresson in Reno, Nevada, during the filming of "The Misfits" in 1960, as well as a portrait of Olga Andreyev Carlisle's aunt
      - 1975-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-39, 48) (Box 78)
        Includes Rumsey Hall School in Washington; pies at the Philips Diner in Woodbury; and the Canfield Corner Pharmacy, operated by Vera Taylor Martiny in North Woodbury; as well as the Clamp's Hamburger Stand and a pond on the estate of Frederic March in New Milford
        Also includes images of museum director Elodie Courter Osborn, probably in Salisbury
      - 1975-02. Pilobolus dance company, including Martha Clarke, choreographer and director, and rehearsing (No rolls recorded) (Box 78)
      - 1975-03. The Seagull, by Anton Chekhov, directed by Joseph Chaikin at the Manhattan Theatre Club (Rolls 1-9) (Box 78)
      - 1975-04. Party by Inge Morath for Vogue magazine (Rolls 1-7) (Box 78)
        Includes Alexander Liberman, magazine editor, publisher, painter, photographer, and sculptor, and his wife, milliner Tatiana Yacovleff du Plessix Liberman; Cleve Gray, painter, and his wife, Francine du Plessix Gray, author and critic; Henry Carlisle, translator and novelist, and his wife, author Olga Andreyev Carlisle; and Philip Roth, novelist
      - 1975-05. Elodie Courter Osborn, museum director, for the MacDowell Colony in Peterborough, New Hampshire (Rolls 1-3) (Box 78)
      - 1975-06. Jay Presson Allen, screenwriter, playwright, stage director, television producer, and novelist (Rolls 1-9) (Box 78)
      - 1975-07. Judy Andreyev's Quartet rehearsal, Paris, France (Rolls 1-5) (Box 78)
      - 1975-08. Paris, France (Rolls 1-4) (Box 78)
        Includes the Eiffel Tower, Jardin du Luxembourg, Montmartre, Palais Garnier, Place du Tertre, Place Saint-Sulpice, and Pont Alexandre III, as well as The Louvre, including artworks, such as Aphrodite (also known as Venus de Milo ), The Three Graces, and portraits by Jean-Auguste-Dominique Ingres
      - 1975-09. Vienna, Austria (No rolls recorded) (Box 78)
        Consists of preliminary work for book, Bilder aus Wien: Der Liebe Augustin (Reich Verlag, Switzerland, 1981)
        Includes Wolfgang Hutter, painter; Arnold Keyserling, philosopher and theologian, and his wife, Wilhelmine von Auersperg Keyserling; Markus Prachensky, painter, and his wife, Brigitte Neundlinger-Prachensky; Prince Joseph Schwarzenberg, III; Prince Max Emanuel of Thurn and Taxis; and Fritz Wotruba, sculptor
        Locations in Vienna include Albertina - Bastei, Arsenal, Belvedere, Burggarten, Burgtheater, Central Cemetery (Zentralfriedhof), Donnerbrunnen, Hofzuckerbäckerei Demel, Kunsthistorisches Museum, Maria-Theresien-Platz, Mozart-Brunnen, Neue Markt, Prater, Rathaus, Ring Road (Ringstraße), Salon of Elsa Thurn, Secessionsgebäude, Stadtbahn Stadtpark, Stephansdom, and Volksgarten
        Other locations in Austria include Maria Enzersdorf and the Spanish Riding School (Spanische Hofreitschule) in Heldenberg
      - 1975-10. Death of a Salesman, by Arthur Miller, directed by George C. Scott, at Circle in the Square Theatre, New York City (Rolls 1-11) (Box 78)
        Includes Kōbō Abe, writer, playwright, and photographer, with actress Raquel Welch in Manhattan, New York City, discussing an eponymous movie based on his novel The Woman in the Dunes (1962), as well as Alfred Eisenstaedt photographing Arthur Miller in Roxbury
      - 1975-11. Colorado (Rolls 1-2) (Box 78)
        Includes images of Leadville
      - 1975-12. Ah, Wilderness!, by Eugene O'Neill, directed by Arvin Brown, at Circle in the Square Theatre, New York City (Rolls 1-8) (Box 79)
        Cast includes Richard Backus, John Braden, Ralph Drischell, Geraldine Fitzgerald, Don Gantry, Sean G. Griffin, Linda Hunt, Swoosie Kurtz, Suzanne Lederer, Stephen Mendillo, Paul Rudd, William Swetland, Christina Whitmore, Teresa Wright, and Glenn Zachar
      - 1975-13. Telling a Fable About a Journey, a collaborative music-theater work by Jean-Claude Van ltallie and Richard Peaslee, directed by Joseph Chaikin, at Exchange Theater (Westbeth), New York City (Rolls 1-5) (Box 79)
      - 1975-14. The Sculpture and Drawings of Elie Nadelman at the Whitney Museum of American Art, New York City, as well as images of Louisa James Calder (Roll 1) (Box 79)
      - 1975-15. The Glass Menagerie, by Tennessee Williams, at the Circle in the Square Theatre, New York City, directed by Theodore Mann (Rolls 1-19) (Box 79)
        Includes cast members Maureen Stapleton and Rip Torn
      - 1975-16. Zoya Boguslavskaya, writer and wife of Andrei Voznesensky (Rolls 1-2) (Box 79)
      - 1976-01. Connecticut (Rolls 1-2) (Box 79)
      - 1976-02. The Lady from the Sea, written Henrik Ibsen, directed by Tony Richardson, at the Circle in the Square Theatre (Rolls 1-18) (Box 79)
        Includes Pat Hingle, actor, and actress Vanessa Redgrave
      - 1976-03. Augusta Talbot, sculptor and painter (Rolls 1-5) (Box 79)
      - 1976-04. Dr. Richard Young, professor of Chinese (Rolls 1-2) (Box 79)
      - 1976-05. Francine du Plessix Gray, author (Rolls 1-5) (Box 79)
        Includes portraits for cover of her novel, Lovers and Tyrants (New York: Simon and Schuster, 1976)
      - 1976-06. Party in New York, with Henry Kissinger, United States Secretary of State (Roll 1) (Box 79)
      - 1976-07. Arthur Miller meeting with Syrian poet Ali Ahmad Said Esber, also known as Adonis or Adunis, and an Egyptian journalist (No rolls recorded) (Box 79)
      - 1976-08. Pal Joey, musical with a book by John O'Hara and music and lyrics by Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart at the Circle in the Square Theatre, New York City (Rolls 1-5) (Box 79)
      - 1976-09. Anne Richardson Roiphe, writer and journalist (Rolls 1-3) (Box 79)
        Probably photographed for her novel, Torch Song (New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1977)
      - 1976-10. Nantucket, Massachusetts (No rolls recorded) (Box 79)
      - 1976-11. Days in the Trees, by Marguerite Duras, directed by Stephen Porter, at Circle in the Square Theatre, New York City (No rolls recorded) (Box 79)
      - 1976-12. Han Suyin, author and physician (Rolls 1-2) (Box 79)
      - 1976-13. Alexander Calder, sculptor (No rolls recorded) (Box 79)
        Includes the last photographs made on November 7, 1976, of Calder before his death
      - 1977-01. Personal photographs (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
        Includes Paris, France; Bibi Anderson, actress, and preparations for staging of The Archbishop's Ceiling, by Arthur Miller
      - 1977-02. Israel (Rolls 1-8) (Box 80)
      - 1977-03. Arthur Miller (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-04. Rebecca Miller and Arthur Miller (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
        Created with Leica Motor
      - 1977-05. Bella Akhmadulina, poet, short story writer, and translator (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
        Includes Werner Morath, brother of Inge Morath
      - 1977-06. Ondekoza, a Japanese troupe specializing in taiko drumming (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-07. William Sloane Coffin, clergyman and peace activist (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
        Includes Rebecca Miller and Arthur Miller in studio
      - 1977-08. Washington, D.C. (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-09. The Archbishop's Ceiling, by Arthur Miller, at the John F. Kennedy Center, Washington, D.C. (Rolls 1-6) (Box 80)
        Includes Bella Akhmadulina, poet, short story writer, and translator; Werner Morath, brother of Inge Morath, and National Air and Space Museum
      - 1977-10. Kōbō Abe, writer, playwright, photographer and inventor, at a rehearsal of his play, Images (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-11. Takarazuka Grand Theater and Takarazuka Music School in Takarazuka, Hyōgo Prefecture, Japan (Rolls 1-14) (Box 80)
      - 1977-12. Japan (Rolls 1-8) (Box 80)
        Includes locations in Mount Aso, Beppu, Hiroshima, Itsukushima (also known as Miyajima), Seto Inland Sea, Tokyo, and Usuki with Katharine "Kay" Brown, literary agent of Arthur Miller
      - 1977-13. Vladimir Horowitz, pianist and composer, and Isaac Stern, violinist and conductor (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-14. Up from Paradise, musical with a book and lyrics by Arthur Miller and music by Stanley Silverman, Music Theater Lab workshop at the John F. Kennedy Center, Washington, D.C. (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-15. Stanley Silverman, composer (Roll 3) (Box 80)
      - 1977-16. Gretchen Cryer, playwright, lyricist, and actress, and Nancy Ford, composer, in New York (Rolls 1-4) (Box 80)
      - 1977-17. Marge Neikrug, gallery owner (Roll 2) (Box 80)
      - 1977-18. Andrei Voznesensky, poet and writer (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-19. Arthur Miller and Vincent Gardenia, actor, performing Letter to U Thant by Mikis Theodorakis for Amnesty International (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)
      - 1977-20. The Dybbuk, translation by Mira Rafalowicz, produced by Joseph Chaikin at The Public Theater in New York City (No rolls recorded) (Box 80)